欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内
前情提要
PREVIOUSLY ON GHOSTS
你愿意让我成为这里
Will you make me the happiest ghost
-最幸福的鬼鬼吗  -不
on the entire property? No.
我愿意让你成为第二幸福的
I will make you the second happiest.
杀死你的人是我儿子托马斯
Your killer was my son Thomas.
一直以来你都知道但却从没有告诉过我
You've known this this whole time and never told me?
非常抱歉 阿尔伯塔
I'm very sorry, Alberta.
不 抱歉的是我
No, I'm sorry.
抱歉我竟然把你当成了我的朋友
Sorry I ever considered you to be a friend.
你好性感
You're so hot.
索尔和花花都非常熟悉猫头鹰
Thor and Flower both familiar with owls.
基本上就是我们关系的基础
Is definitely basis for entire relationship.
我觉得其中一个鬼鬼刚刚被吸上天了
I think one of the ghosts just got sucked off.
-谁  -不知道啊
Who? I have no idea.
我希望是特雷弗
I hope it's Trevor.
谁都不在 我去书房看看
No one's in here. I'll check the library.
好 我去厨房
Okay, I'll check the kitchen!
-书房里没鬼  -我反正也看不到鬼
Library's empty. I can't see ghosts.
不知道我进去干嘛
I don't know why I went in there.
你们这么激动干嘛
What's all the hubbub? Oh!
皮特和萨萨刚从楼梯上下来
Pete and Sass just came down the stairs,
-所以不是他们俩  -太好了
so it wasn't them. Oh, thank God.
-嘿  -特雷弗也来了
Hey. And there's Trevor, too.
-行吧  -出什么事了
Okay. What's going on?
我们看见一道光 有鬼鬼被吸上天了
We saw a light. Someone just got sucked off.
好吧 那我们得报个数了
PETE: Okay, we need a head count.
所有鬼都看看跟你们好的同伴在不在
Everybody find your suck- off buddy!
都下来吧
Guys, get down here.
真不敢相信居然有鬼不在了
I can't believe one of them is gone.
先别慌 也许只是地下室的鬼呢
Let's not panic. Maybe it was just a basement ghost.
只是地下室的鬼
"Just a basement ghost"?
天 我不是那个意思
Oh, God, that's not what I meant.
真敢说啊 皮特 真行
Real nice, Pete. Real nice.
难以置信
Unbelievable!
我们刚刚弄清楚是谁杀的我
We just solved my murder.
我一个姑娘家到底要怎么做才能升天呢
What's a girl got to do to get sucked off around here?
我也在
I, too, am here,
尽管我刚刚过了一百年
despite bravely revealing after a mere hundred years
我就勇敢的揭穿杀死阿尔伯塔的是我儿子
that my son was Alberta's murderer all along. SASAPPIS: Yes,
-是 你才是故事的主角  -可是
you're the hero of that storyJAY: I mean,
我们给特雷弗举办了葬礼
we had a funeral for Trevor.
我们了结了他的心愿啊
I mean, we gave him so much closure.
我还在喔 哥们 接受现实吧
Still here, bro. Deal with it.
好吧 杰 我们还没看到艾萨克
Okay, Jay, so far we're still missing Isaac,
索尔和花花
Thor and Flower.
撞撞来了
Oh, there's Crash.
我刚刚把头卡阁楼上了
So, I just stuck my head in the attic.
是真的
Literally.
你看到斯蒂芬妮了吗
Did you see Stephanie?
那个恐怖的链锯舞会女吗
The creepy chain saw prom girl?
应该跟平时一样还在睡觉吧
Still sleeping, as usual.
她一出来就跟个没插电的点唱机一样
That bird is out like an unplugged jukebox.
奈杰尔
Nigel!
Nigel?
奈杰尔 有鬼见到奈杰尔了吗
Nigel? Has anyone seen Nigel?
希金图上校
Captain Higgintoot!
奈杰尔 奈杰尔
Nigell Nigel!
我回棚屋去显摆我们订婚的事去了
NIGEL: I went to the shed to boast of our betrothal
可回来的路上 我看见一道白光
but on my way back, I saw the white light.
真是担心死我了
I feared for the worst.
你能想象的到 如果在我们的订婚之夜
Could you imagine, one of us sucked off
其中一个被吸走是多么的悲伤
on the night of our engagement? NANCY: Well,
我的地下室朋友们也都在呢
all my basement friends are accounted for.
抱歉了皮特
Sorry, Pete.
那就只剩索尔和花花了
So, that leaves Thor and Flower.
杰 看上去
Jay, it seems like
不是索尔就是花花了
it's either Thor or Flower. JAY: Whoa.
八大主角之一啊
One of the main eight.
有人见到花花了吗
Anyone seen Flower?
我想给她看看厨房里的蝴蝶呢
Want to show her butterfly in pantry.
怎么了
What?
索尔 你是最后一个见到花花的
SASAPPIS: Thor, you were the last one to see Flower.
发生什么大事了吗
Did anything significant happen?
灵魂启迪或者突然顿悟之类的
Personal revelations or sudden epiphanies?
索尔觉得没有
Thor don't think so.
那你跟她说的最后一句是什么
Well, what was the last thing you said to her?
应该是跟鳕鱼有关的
Believe it was comment about cod
具体的好像是鳕鱼的味道
Specifically, flavor of cod.
再具体点 说鳕鱼很好吃
Specifically, that flavor is good.
要是我也会直接上天堂了
I know that would shoot me straight to paradise.
真为花花高兴
PETE: I'm happy for Flower,
但我会想她的
but I'm gonna miss her.
而且她肯定也会想我们的
And I bet she'll miss us,
如果她还能记得我们的话
if she remembers who we are.
她上周是管你叫戴维来着
She did call you Dave last week. Yeah.
然后她又说 抱歉 汤姆
But then she said, "I'm sorry, Tom. "
至少她知遒你不叫戴维
So at least she knew Dave wasn't right. Hmm.
那一个鬼鬼上天堂之后该怎么做呢
So, like, what normally happens after a ghost moves on?
是有什么仪式吗
Is there some sort of ceremony?
已经很久没搞过了 但我们一般会聚集在一起 说几句话
It's been a long time, but we gather, say a few words,
就跟纪念活人没什么区别
much like a memorial for a Living.
尽管从小点心的角度来说不太一样
Though there's not much in the way of finger foods,
因为我们不会做小点心
because we can't make finger foods
也没法抓住小点心
or hold finger foods
或者吃掉小点心
or consume finger foods.
要是能吃块丽兹饼干我什么都愿意做
The things I would do to a Ritz cracker.
发生在花花身上的事
SASAPPIS: Look, what happened to Flower
是我们都想要的
is what we all want for ourselves,
但也同时伴随着一些复杂的情绪
but it comes with a lot of complicated emotions.
这太不公平了 她在这才50年吧
This is unfair. She was here for, what, 50 years?
我都被困在这一世纪了
I've been stuck in this dump for a damn century.
看来有火嫉妒了
One of which is jealousy.
我很痛苦啊
I feel pain!
另一个很痛苦
Another is pain.
好吧 不是我麻木不仁哈
Okay, not to be insensitive,
但你觉得今晚我们的订婚派对
but do you get the sense that our engagement party
还能搞起来吗
is still on for tonight?
目前看起来好像这不是大家最关心的
It doesn't appear to be foremost on people's minds.
悲伤
Sorrow!
我感觉真是挺难过的
It's just that I feel bad
因为萨曼莎把派对的布置都买好了
because Samantha purchased all those party supplies
两个气球哎
NIGEL: The two balloons.
是 是 是
Yes. Yes, yes.
嘿 可能是我想多了 但你们觉得
Hey, I might just be in my head, but do you think
南希会不会告诉地下室的鬼鬼们
Nancy told the rest of the pit about
我刚才说的那句话呢
my"just a basement ghost"comment?
皮特 别想了
TREVOR: Pete, let it go.
相信我 兄弟
Trust me, bro,
不会有人想起你的
nobody's ever thinking about you.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿 索尔怎么样了
Hey. How's Thor doing?
毕竟失去了自己的女友
I mean, losing your girlfriend?
毕竟失去了自已的女友
就咱俩说哈 毕竟花花也不可能为了他回来嘛
Between you and me, that is not something you come back from.
行吧 你这话基本上就在他耳边说的
Uh- huh. You are sort of whispering directly in his ear.
抱歉了 大块头
Oh. Sorry, big guy.
索尔 失去一个人是挺难的
HETTY: Thor, loss is never easy,
但正如我曾经对那对因为孩子
but as I once told the grieving parents
在工厂做童工被拖进了织机里悲伤不已的父母说过的话
of a child factory worker who'd been pulled into a loom...
想到有人离开是很难过的事
You know, it's hard when we think someone's gone.
随便吧 你想接话你就接
By all means, take the floor.
但是在印度教
But in Hinduism,
我们曾经学到过 当一个人死去
we're taught that when a person dies,
他们的灵魂会找到一个新家
their spirit finds a new home,
在一个不同的身体里
in a different body.
可能是人类 可能是动物
Could be human, could be an animal.
可能是任何东西 这就叫轮回
Could be anything. It's called reincarnation.
你可以想像花花
It's nice to think that Flower might be
可能就在你身边
closer than you know.
帮我谢谢小个子 但很遗憾
Please thank small man, but, unfortunately,
他没能安抚索尔的痛苦
he not ease Thor's pain.
世界仍然很灰暗
World still dark.
爱情已死
Love still dead.
希望被抛弃
Hope abandoned.
那你跟那可怜孩子的父母到底说了什么
So, uh, what did you tell that poor kid's parents?
我跟他们说现在你们的另一个孩子
Ooh. I told them there's a job opening
有工作机会了
for your other child,
这次你们可记得给他们剪短头发
and this time, be sure to cut their hair.
他们笑中带泪的
They cried with joy.
咚咚 大家看上去都不错嘛
PETE: Knock, knock! Everybody decent?
忘了味道的事了
Wow. I forget about the smell.
当然 味道也很不错
It's a good smell, of course.
我是说 我 我喜欢
I mean, I...I- I like it.
-你来干嘛 皮特  -没啥事
What do you want, Pete? Nothing.
就是过来看看大家好不好
Uh, just, uh, coming to see how everyone's doing.
你能来看我们可真不错
Nice of you to check in.
毕竟我们只是地下室的鬼鬼
Especially since we're just basement ghosts.
天 所以你还是说了
Oh, boy. So you did say something.
我又没有义务保护你 皮特
It's not my job to protect you, Pete.
再说了 这话题多劲爆
Plus, it was a juicy nugget,
毕竟聊了几小时的热水器后
and after a few hours of water heater talk,
你总得找点其它话题来充实下日子吧
you start looking for other stuff to fill your day.
说到这
CHOLERA VICTIM NIGEL: Speaking of which,
其他人有注意到那个热水器
did anyone else notice that gurgle
今早发出的咕嘟咕嘟的水声吗
the water heater was making this morning?
我们已经讨论过水声了
We already discussed the gurgle!
该死 这里可真无聊啊
Damn it, it's boring down here.
马克刚刚带人过来了
Yes! Mark just got here with his crew.
他们今天就要装修谷仓了吗
Oh, they're starting renovations on the barn today?
我们就要有家饭店了 宝儿
We're gonna have a restaurant, babe.
真是个糟糕的投资
Terrible investment.
我的朋友想让我加入一个
My friend tried to get me to go in
布法罗狂野鸡翅的项目
on something called Buffalo Wild Wings.
那项目怎么可能成嘛
Can't imagine that worked out for him.
我天
Oh, my God!
这就是前厅了
And this is the front hallway.
刚刚在前台后面尖叫的那个
That, of course, is Samantha
当然就是萨曼莎了
that just screamed behind the desk.
你们好啊
Hello.
皮特刚刚带上来一群霍乱鬼
Pete just walked in with a whole clump of cholera ghosts.
欢迎哈
I mean, welcome.
皮特 你这是搞什么呢 嗨
Pete, what the hell is going on? Hi.
你你你们不如去“活”动室里
Um, wh- wh- wh- why don't you guys make yourselves comfy
舒服待会儿啊
in the living room?
别介意那个“活”字儿哈
: Don't let that name offend you.
我马上就回来带你们继续参观哈
I'lI be back to resume the tour in a jiff.
这地板肯定是松木的
These floors got to be pine.
这哪是松木 斯图尔特
They're not pine, Stuart.
不懂就憋瞎说了
Know your wood or shut up about it.
这么回事 我去了趟地下室
Okay, so I went down to the basement
想确保他们没生我气
to make sure they weren't mad at me about
就因为我说那句地下室的鬼
the whole "just a basement ghost"comment.
结果没想到 他们特别生气
Well, turns out, they were, in fact, very mad.
谁在乎他们是不是生你的气啊
Well, who cares if they're mad at you?
再说了 对他们来说愤怒这种情绪
Also, anger is a very complex emotion
有点过于复杂了
to assign to them.
我不想让别人生我气啊
Well, I don't like anybody being mad at me,
所以我想向他们证明 我其实挺喜欢他们的
so to prove to them how much I enjoy them,
然后就邀请他们来楼上了
I kind of invited them to come upstairs.
但别担心 我 我确定
But don't worry, I- I'm sure
他们很快会下楼的
they're gonna be going back downstairs very soon.
我们能看会楼上的电视吗
Mind if we go watch that TV thing upstairs?
当然可以 看吧 放松一下
Sure. Yeah. Kick back, relax,
想待多久就多久
stay as long as you like.
-我真的不擅长处理冲突哎  -嘿 两位
I'm not great with conflict. MARK: Hey, guys.
嘿 马克
Hey, Mark.
谷仓那边怎么样了
How are things out in the barn?
嘿 你刚来15分钟
Hey, you've been here 15 minutes.
不是现在就想说我们有什么麻烦吧
Do not tell me that we have a problem.
我们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
这事搞的
Walked into that one.
跟我来 我指给你看
Come with me, I'll show you.
那是猫头鹰吗
Is that an owl?
从外形来看就是普通的谷仓猫头鹰
Common barn owl by the look of it.
学名叫仓鹗
Binomial name is Tyto alba.
我在宾大上过一门鸟类学
I took an ornithology class at Penn
因为上课的都是三角洲女性联谊会的姑娘
'cause it was packed with Tri- Deltas.
出什么事了
What's happening?
工程暂停了
Construction's held up
因为他们发现了一只猫头鹰在筑巢
cause they found an owl nesting.
是嘛
THORFINN: Really?
猫头鹰
Owl.
很明显我们得帮忙搬迁了
MARK: Obviously, we'll need to relocate it.
一旦他们开始栖息 你就得把它们
Once they've started roosting, you've got to
挪的远远的 否则它们还会
move them miles away, otherwise they just come
飞回到原来的位置
right back to the same spot.
你没事吧大块头
You okay, big guy?
喜欢猫头鹰
Love for owls
是花花和索尔发现的第一个共同点
first thing Flower and Thorfinn find in common.
对我们来说意义重大
Means great deal to us.
-是啊  -感觉像是某种征兆
Yeah. Feels like...sign.
这么着吧 萨曼
JAY: You know what, uh, Sam,
咱们还有帮忙处理鸽子那家伙的
do we still have the number of the guy who helped us
手机号吧
get rid of the pigeons?
默夫 有 我这就给他打个电话
Murph. Yeah, sure, I'll give him a call.
实际上 我再一想 还有吗
Actually, let me think. Do I still have it?
发生的事情显而易见
Tis obvious what has happened.
在花花升天之后几小时
Hours after Flower sucked off,
她最喜欢的动物出现在谷仓
her favorite animal appear in barn.
这跟杰预言的一样
It is just as Jay predicted.
猫头鹰不是预兆
Owl not sign.
猫头鹰就是花花
Owl is Flower.
花花就是猫头鹰
Flower is Owl!
杰 我们可能又有另一个麻烦了
Jay, we might have another problem.
轮回
Reincarnation!
可以说是好消息坏消息参半吧
Okay, so it's kind of a good news- bad news situation.
好消息是
The good news is that
索尔对于你说的
Thor really took
轮回那事儿还真挺上心的
your thoughts on reincarnation to heart.
花花好像有点饿了
Look like Flower little hungry.
不如你杀只老鼠来喂她啊
Maybe you slay mouse to feed her?
嗯嗯 坏消息是
Uh- huh. The bad news is,
索尔认为那只猫头鹰
Thor thinks that that owl
就是花花
is Flower.
他认为他女友轮回
JAY: He thinks that his girlfriend reincarnated
变成了猫头鹰吗
into an owl?
-一只成年的猫头鹰  -而且他要求
A- A fully grown adult owl? And he's demanding
我们不能把它挪走或者以任何方式打扰到它
that we don't move or in any way disturb it. Sam,
萨曼 马克的人都着急等着呢
Mark's guys are on the clock.
他们租了一堆重型建筑设备
They rented a bunch of heavy construction equipment,
如果不挪走猫头鹰 我们真是分分钟都在损失钱
and we're losing money every hour that we don't move
萨曼莎 别溜号
that owl. THORFINN: Samantha, please focus.
你还要杀老鼠去呢
You have mice to slaughter.
你觉得花花猫头鹰会想吃老鼠
Do you think Flower the Owl would want mice
还是想吃素呢
or maybe like a vegetarian option?
这问题问的好
Is excellent question.
萨曼 让杰做两手准备吧
Sam, have Jay prepare both.
你也觉得那是花花吗
Do you actually think that that's Flower?
不是 但我想看索尔和猫头鹰约会
No, but I don't want Thor to stop dating an owl.
就是吧 索尔现在
It's just that Thor is in
极其脆弱
an extremely delicate place right now.
花花 我爱你
Flower, I love you!
你 我爱你
You! I love you!
她好像有点迷糊了
She seem confused.
真是典型的花花啊
: Classic Flower.
我觉得这个哀悼的过程我们不能太着急了
And I just don't think we should rush the grieving process.
也许我们可以把工程推迟一周或者
May- Maybe if we delayed construction by like a week
好吧 我来说
Okay. I'm calling it.
我们不能总是把鬼鬼
We can't always put the ghost stuff
放在人之前
before the people stuff.
所以抱歉了 索尔
So I'm sorry, Thor,
但我们必须得给这只猫头鹰搬个家
but we got to relocate the owl upstate.
你敢动花花 我就把谷仓烧了
You move Flower, I burn down barn.
就跟我烧掉露台一样
Like how I burn down gazebo.
现在索尔说 如果我们搬走花花
Now Thor's saying if we relocate Flower,
他就要把谷仓烧了
he's gonna burn down the barn.
这就是吹牛吧
Well, that's got to be a bluff.
不是吧
Oh, come on.
只是小试牛刀
Is just a taste.
好吧 我来总结一下哈
JAY: Okay, let me just sum up here.
一个一千岁的维京人认为
A thousand- year- old Viking thinks that
他死去的嬉皮士女友现在变成了鸟
his dead hippie girlfriend is now a bird,
而如果我给鸟换个地方以实现我毕生的梦想
and if I move it to achieve my lifelong dream,
他就要烧了我的饭店
he's gonna burn down my restaurant.
总结的非常好
That's well summarized. Mm- hmm.
不知道这么说能不能安慰到你 是你给了索尔希望
If it helps, you've given Thor hope.
安慰不到
It doesn't.
你想办法解决吧 萨曼
Fix this, Sam.
我去求马克让我开会儿挖掘机
I'm gonna go beg Mark to let me ride the excavator,
这一天总得有一件好事吧
'cause I really need a win today.
花花饿了 咔咔
Flower hungry. Chop- chop.
这话是让你快点的意思 但同时也形容了
It mean"move quickly"but also describe action
你砍下老鼠脑袋时发出的声音
you make when you decapitate mouse.
太糟糕了
This is bad.
无法容忍
Intolerable.
那只为什么要站在电视机的正前方呢
Why is that one just standing in front of the television?
嘿 说你呢
You there, hello?
-她喜欢电视发出的光  -嘿 你能挪挪吗
She likes the glow. Hey, could you scooch?
德克的屁股只有一半在沙发上
Dirk only has one cheek on the couch.
还挺好的
DIRK: It's kind of nice.
让我觉得屁股中间有一股小风
It's creating a breeze down Main Street.
-忍不了了  -行了
Nope. HETTY: Okay!
虽然说我们在一起
While it's been nice,
还挺开心的
all of us being here together,
但我觉得你们是时候
I think it's time for some of us to return
回到自己该回的“潮”穴了吧
to the dank pit from whence we came.
你们听见她说的了 快走
You heard her. Scram!
抱歉 但我们是皮特邀请来的客人
Sorry, but we're Pete's invited guests.
对 是他让我们来的
DIRK: Yeah, he wants us up here.
所以直接离开有点不礼貌
And it would be rude to leave.
-对  -皮特
Yeah. Peter!
我们为什么来地下室啊
Why are we in the basement?
就因为你 这是唯一一间
Because, thanks to you, this is the one room
看不到一群拥挤的
in the house that isn't teeming
穿着土豆袋的妖精的屋子了
with potato sack- wearing hobgoblins.
皮特 你必须让他们离开
Peter, you must tell them to go.
其中一个还让我帮忙挠后背的疮
One of them asked me to scratch their back sores.
我都不知道该说什么 我只好照做了 我都慌了
I didn't know what to say. I did it. Ipanicked.
如果过了一段时间
ISAAC: What if they're still up there once enough time
他们还待那不肯走
has passed for it to be appropriate to proceed
我要怎么搞订婚派对啊 顺便跟进一下
with an engagement party? And, follow- up,
你们觉得我们什么时候开派对合适
how- how- how long do we think that is?
好吧 我承认 这对我来说
Okay, I admit this hasn't been a Club Med vacation
也不是美达假日村
for me either.
更像是桑道斯 不予置评
More like Sandals, no comment.
我的手指头现在闻起来还怪怪的
My fingers still smell weird.
我不能直接让他们回楼下来
I can't just tell them to come back downstairs.
他们会生我气的
They'll be mad at me.
如果你不说 那我们就要生你气了
Well, if you don't, then we'll be mad at you.
老天 这可让我如何是好啊
Criminy, this is one dill of a pickle.
-皮特  -我天
Pete. Oh, my...
这样吧
Here's the deal.
他们得离开了
They got to go.
等等 什么 你 你也不想让他们待在楼上吗
Wait, what? You, you don't want them up there either?
你下来这干嘛
What are you doing down here?
楼上本来是我偶尔去喘息一下的地方
Upstairs used to be the place I could take a break.
我可以稍微远离这些妖怪们一会儿
My respite from those weirdos.
但现在我没有避难所了
But now I have no sanctuary.
看见没 它都忍受不了它们 掉转枪口了
See? Even it can't stand them. It's turning on its own.
听着 皮特
NANCY: Look, Pete,
不管你怎么做
no matter what you do,
都会让一部分人不痛快的
you're gonna piss someone off.
但如果你惹我生气了 我就在你睡觉时
But if you piss me off, I'm gonna spit
把带着霍乱病菌的口水吐到你嘴里去
cholera juice in your mouth while you sleep.
这威胁真是即可怕又明确
Well, that's a horrifying and clarifying threat.
好吧
Okay.
我去跟他们谈
I'll talk to them.
我刚看到挪鸟窝的人开车走了
I just saw the bird removal guy driving away.
是你解决了吗
Did you take care of it already?
对 谷仓里现在没有猫头鹰了
Yep, the barn is now owl- free.
真是世界上最好的老婆
Best wife ever.
索尔没事吗
And- and Thor's okay?
他没有因为“花头鹰”走了而发火吗
He's not crushed that the Flowl's gone?
我把花花和猫头鹰俩词儿合并了
I'mcombining"Flower"and"owl. "
-聪明  -给个B吧
Kind of clever. Eh, I give it a"B. "
你能后退一步吗
Can you just back up?
没事啊 索尔好像还挺高兴的
No, uh, Thor seems to be in pretty good spirits.
他们把它送到偏僻的地方了吗
Did they take it upstate?
更应该说是当地吧
A little more local than that.
宝儿 我们不能让它再飞回来了
Well, babe, we don't want it to come back.
你说的当地离咱们这有多近
How- how local are we talking?
近的不得了
Pretty local.
萨曼这次又做什么了
What did Sam do this time? Oh, man.
-杰要发火了  -住嘴
Jay is not happy. Stop it.
你们又不了解他们 他们是我们的
You don't know them. They're ours.
我试过喂花头鹰
Well, tried to feed the Flowl.
看来它不喜欢吃大豆做的老鼠
Turns out it does not like soy mice.
当然了
Obviously.
豆制品会严重损坏
Soy wreaks havoc on birds'
鸟类脆弱的内分泌系统
sensitive endocrine systems.
天哪 杰 你还好吧
Oh, my God, Jay, are you okay?
我不好 萨曼
No, I'm not okay, Sam.
我在自己家里被一只小型恐龙袭击了
I was attacked in my own home by a tiny dinosaur
我现在得吃些非常特殊的抗生素
and now I have to take very specific antibiotics.
我们要退房 还要全款退钱
We're checking out and we'd like a full refund.
天哪
Oh, gosh.
出什么问题了吗
Was there some sort of problem?
是不够暖和吗
Was it the heating?
我知道屋里可能会有些漏风
Because I- I know that there can be a bit of a draft.
不 是那只住我们隔壁的
No, it was the large bird of prey
大型猛禽
living in the room next to us.
我们的网站上的确写了
Well, our website does promise
提供与当地动物的亲密接触体验
an immersive experience with the local fauna.
就是与动物的亲密接触
An immersive experience with the local fauna
-才让我得了霍乱  -抱歉 女士
is how I got cholera. JAY: We're sorry, ma'am.
我们会尽快处理猫头鹰的问题
And- and we're gonna take care of the owl problem
还会给您双倍的
and we are going to double
伍德斯通民宿购物积分
your Woodstone Rewards Points.
不用了 我们这就走
Forget it, we're leaving
我知道这是什么表情
Oh, I know that look.
不 你不知道
No, you don't.
宝儿 事态发展越来越严重了
Okay, babe, this is getting kind of crazy.
不能再这样下去了
I mean, this cannot go on.
抱歉 但你不可能简单打个响指
Well, I- I'm sorry, you can't just snap your fingers
就想要别人忘记
and expect somebody to move on when they've just
刚失去好友的悲痛
lost one of their best friends.
我以为这就是你想要的
Whoa, I thought this is what you wanted.
你总说你的目标就是帮助他们放下过去
You've always said your mission is to help them move on.
我的确是这样想的 可是这并不简单
It is what I want, but that doesn't mean it's easy.
宝儿 你不会真的相信
Babe, you don't really think
那只猫头鹰就是花花吧
that that owl is Flower, do you?
不是的
No.
但我理解索尔的心情
But I get why Thor wants it to be.
宝儿 你想帮助索尔
JAY: Aw, babe. It's great
是很好 但我觉得
you want to help Thor, but I think
他真正需要的是迈过这道坎 继续生活
what he really needs is help moving on.
-我们会陪着你的  -滚一边去
We're here for you. Go away
嘿 大家
PETE: Hello, everyone. Um
我只想说
I- I- I just wanted to say that I am, um,
我很开心你们接受我的邀请上楼来玩
so happy you all took me up on my invitation to come upstairs.
别磨叽了 赶快把那些怪物赶走
Quit dithering and banish the monsters.
还有
And, um
有你们陪伴真的很好
it has been great having you.
是这样的 伙计们
Okay, uh, here's the deal, you guys.
楼上现在要应付的事情太多了
We kind of got a lot going on right now.
萨曼和杰在吵架
Um, Sam and Jay are fighting.
屋里还有只该死的猫头鹰在游荡
There's a gosh darn owl in the house.
更别说我们刚刚失去亲爱的朋友花花
Not to mention we just lost our dear friend Flower.
就是戴眼镜的那只嬉皮鬼
She was the, the hippie one with the glasses?
无所谓了 重点是
It doesn't matter, the point is...
我们认识花花
We knew Flower.
真的吗
You did?
是啊 她总去看我们
Yeah, she visited us all the time.
一开始 我们是因为集体生活和撕裂伤而有共同话题
At first, we mainly bonded over communal living and open wounds,
后来就慢慢变成了朋友
but then...we became friends.
她是我见过最友善的人
She was one of the kindest people I've ever met.
她对我们都一视同仁
She never treated us different.
她人很好 我们都会很想念她的
She was a good one, and we'll miss her very much.
是啊
CATHERINE: Yeah.
你想告诉我们什么 皮特
So what did you want to tell us, Pete?
哦我的天哪 你们会很难承受的
Ah, cheese and crackers, this is gonna be hard.
皮特是想说
What Pete wanted to say was
我们要为花花办一场追悼会
...we're having a memorial for Flower.
想要邀请你们一同参加
And we'd like to invite you all to join us.
因为你们和我们
Because you...
都是一样的人
are people.
这还不够让我升天吗
Okay, that doesn't get me sucked off? l
我都成长了啊
That was growth.
索尔 有时间吗
SAMANTHA: Hey, Thor. Got a minute?
他就坐在笼子旁边
He's, uh, sitting over by the cage.
嘿 索尔
Uh, hey, Thor.
我知道你们的文化十分残酷
I know yours was a brutal culture
习惯了不在意其他人的感受
that didn't care about the suffering of others.
谢谢
Thank you.
但我知道你爱花花
But I know you loved Flower.
虽然我不如你一样了解她
Now, I didn't know her as well as you did. I mean,
她有一次把我搞嗨了 我也听说她有时
she got me high once, and I was told that she watched basketball
会坐在我旁边看篮球比赛 但就我所听说的
near me on occasion, but from everything I've heard about her,
她有一个无拘无束的灵魂
she seems like a real free spirit.
所以
So.
如果这只猫头鹰真的是花花
if this owl really is Flower,
你不觉得我们应该
then don't you think that we owe it to her
让她自由飞翔吗
to let her spirit be free?
杰说的对
Jay's right. I mean.
花花每天都开开/心心的
Flower was the happiest person I know.
再看看她 你觉得她开心吗
And look at her. Does she look happy to you?
不 她不开心
No, she does not.
我们都知道得放她走 大块头
I think we both know what we got to do, big guy.
杰 你干嘛呢
Jay, what are you doing?
我在拍拍他的肩膀表示支持
I'm patting his shoulder supportively.
没拍到吗
Right?
本该能拍到的 但他刚才站起来了
Well, you would have been, but he stood up a while ago
你现在只是在拍他的屁股
and now you're just sort of slapping his ass.
索尔不介意
THORFINN: Thor not mind.
很感谢他的举动
Thor appreciate gesture.
无所谓 我们现在是好朋友了
Whatever. We're bonding.
这是张疑犯照片吗
TREVOR: Is that a mug shot?
我在网上只能
Oh, it was the only photo of Flower
找到这一张花花的照片了
I could find on the Internet.
她那会儿显然已经磕嗨了
She was high, apparently,
一件衣服也没穿 还想要
and naked and tried to join
加入梅西百货的感恩节大游行
the Macy's Thanksgiving Parade.
这才是咱们熟悉的女孩儿
Ah, that's our girl.
打扰了 大家
Excuse me, everyone. Clink, clink. Um
如果说花花有教给我们什么 那就是
if Flower taught us anything, it was to celebrate
生命的美好瞬间永远值得庆贺
life's happy moments.
她不会想要她的追悼会低沉伤感
She would not want this to be a somber affair.
说不定她会希望这是一场
In fact, she might even want it to be
共同纪念会以及订婚仪式
a combined memorial/engagement party.
艾萨克 给我坐好了 下周再搞你说的那些
Isaac, sit your ass down. We'll do your thing next week.
就这么定了
We'll take it.
其实下周是我的生日
It's actually my birthday next week.
别这样好吗
Oh, come on.
花花是我认识的最有耐心的人
Flower was one of the most patient people I ever knew.
I mean, she would just sit and listen for hours 她能坐在那里
几个小时
as I talked about everything from
听我从飞蝇钓鱼和旅行支票
fly- fishing and traveler's checks
说到定向运动和国际ATM费用
to orienteering and international ATM fees.
我觉得大多数时间里
And I think for most of those hours,
她都是清醒着在听我讲话
she was aware of what was going on.
咱们的姑娘意志坚定
Our girl was strong- willed,
对自己要做的事情一心一意
single- minded in her focus.
她知道自己永远追不到那只蝴蝶的
She knew she was never gonna catch that butterfly,
可是
but, man,
她仍旧一直在追着
did she never stop chasing it.
和你们所有人相比
Well, I've only been here a short time,
我来这儿的时间不长
compared to all of you,
但我失去她的伤痛甚至更甚
and maybe loss still hits me harder
因为我很少遇到这样的事
because I've had less of it.
但我也有所经历
But I have had some.
我活在世上的这些年也让我明白
And I've lived long enough to know to cherish
要珍惜那些闯入你生命的人
the special people who come into your life.
因为在你不经意间 或许就会失去他们
Because before you know it, they're gone.
被困在这里千年之久
After a millennium trapped in this world,
索尔已经不期待生活有什么改变了
Thor not expect much to change.
可我遇到了花花 那感觉就像
But then I meet Flower, and was like...
数月昏暗无光的严冬
first light after months of.
突然照进了一缕阳光
sunless winters.
她教会索尔
She taught Thor
他一千年来
things he hadn't learned
都没学会的道理
in a thousand years
看到了千年来
and positions unseen
都没看到过的东西
in a thousand orgies.
说得真好
That's...sweet.
我会想念她的
THORFINN: I will miss her
永永远远
forever.
再见了 花花
THORFINN: Goodbye, Flower.
他们就这么一直待在楼上了吗
So, are they just upstairs all the time now,
那些诡异的地下室鬼鬼们
the creepy basement ghosts?
你这话就是正对着他们的耳朵说的
You just whispered that directly into one of their ears,
不过 事实的确如此
but, yes, I think so.
你刚刚说了什么 皮特
What did you just say, Pete? !
什么 我什么都没说啊
What? I didn't say anything.
你现在仍旧希望
You still wish it was
升天的是地下室的鬼鬼吗
just a basement ghost that got sucked off?
什么 我没说
What? No!
我以为这事已经过去了呢
I thought we were past this.
搞什么
What the hell?
这也太无礼了
That's very rude.
是啊 我也听到了
Yes, I heard it, too.
还是在我们聚在一起的时间里 耻辱
And on this day of coming together. Shame,
皮特 真是耻辱
Peter, shame.
今天的追悼会你什么都没学到吗
Did you learn nothing today?
好了 所有人
NANCY: AII right, everyone.
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
回到我们的地下室去
Back to the basement we go.
好了
AlI right. Aw.
咱们离开这儿
Let's get out of here.
这群人把我们当垃圾一样看待
They're treating us like trash.
我们才不是
And we're not trash.
对吧
Right?
接下来的一百年
They are gonna curse
他们会一直咒骂着你的名字的 皮特
your name for the next 100 years, Pete,
但我总得有所行动
but I had to do something.
演紧身胸衣和男爵时
I'll see you guys
再见咯
for Bodices and Baronstonight?
这小姑娘可真机智啊
It's a clever little thing.